The 1st Masai Mayu Limit
Masai Mayu Limit
Not only her, but Kuro was also in it.
Let's come to the 4th group
Loud Monster Blue Zipper
Manaka Manners
Good work!
SKE48 Miki Ito
Yes!
How about you, Manaka? This event.
You are the oldest person at the venue at 25 years old,
I'd like to prove that I've endured and survived for 25 years
I'd like to prove that I've endured and survived for 25 years by my jumping endurance and strength of mind.
How about you, Fruit Zipper Nakagawa?
I think Manabee is better at flying than running.
I definitely hope he can make up for it here and go to the top!
Wait a minute, please.
Seino!
Manabee, go for it!
They're united with the cheering section... and they're shouting, "Go, Manabee!
Mr. Ito?
How's it going, Mr. Ito?
In SK-VT, in the song "I can't be a poet who speaks with his voice"...
There are a lot of jumps in the song.
The poet's jumps are a specialty of SK-VT.
I'd like to show you the jumps that I've been trained to do.
I'd like to show you the jumps I've been trained to make today.
Everyone is cheering for me!
And now we go to standby... for Manakan Mana and Miki Ito.
Prepare for the fourth set of infinite jumps.
And they're in.
Here we go.
It's not easy to get the rhythm right.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
10, 11, 12, 13, 14
He says his strongest points are his real and memorable thoughts
Dance leader and loud monster
Self-proclaimed ng person, says he is a man of love who will do anything
As for Miki Ito, she said her biggest lift is her endurance
Finished Tokyo Marathon in 5 hours, 29 minutes and 49 seconds
33 34
30-meter run in 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 4 7, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53
50 times approaching
56 57 58 59 60
Both went 60
61 62 63 64 65 66 67 68 69 70
Both coming up on 70
71 72 73 74
75 76 77 78 79 80
We've gone over 81!
They both go over!
Manaka Mana has no sight of Miki Ito at all.
back to back
Miki Ito has no view at all!
She's only looking at par!
Oh no! Oh no!
We're up to 93.
Ninety-five.
Both going over 100.
Ninety-seven.
Not yet.
Ninety-eight.
very close
That's great. - That's great.
Can we get over 200?
Cut! Not yet.
The bar is broken. You're disqualified.
100!
I still got it!
The bar is broken, so this is a disqualification.
Miki Ito breaks 100!
She's over 100!
She's got endurance.
104, 105, 106, 107, 108, 109, 109, 1010
The photo was very popular on x as a little too much!
114 115
116 Iwamoto's record is 129
He is up to 120! If he flies 9 more times!
Iwamoto will be surpassed! Here it comes!
126 127.
128 129
131 132
133 134
135 136
137 138
139 141
142 143
144 145
I stuck it out at 145.
A wonderful record.
144 times has been reached, Miki Ito.
Average chance
He's lived up to his reputation.
Miki Mio is shaking hands with him now.
I've been through a lot of hardship myself, so I'm impressed.
Is this the same girl who has been doing this for a long time? She's got a different stamina. Strong legs, tall.
After the first round, she started to get into the fun mode, and after the 100th round, she was having fun.
His smile was impressive. Thank you very much.
Thank you. How is Nishii?
He really hates buckets. He's a gutsy guy. I was very impressed.
He's got a big smile. It's really...
I paid for it. It was wonderful.
I've decided that I will definitely win the first place somewhere.
I wanted to make a difference so that I could definitely win first place.
I worked so hard.
It's so frustrating.
I'm so disappointed.
Did you feel like you could have done better?
We still made it.
How many times did you get to do it?
I think I did about 150.
I don't know.
Do you think there's room for more?
I didn't even get to the part where you sit down and sit down afterwards.
I'm super frustrated.
I'll do the exact same position tomorrow.
Okay, let's go prone!
I'll leave you to it.
This is the line, right?
That's right. But it peaked at 60.
Suddenly at 60?
I thought I was in trouble, and once I hit 100, I really got into the mode and didn't feel anything, but that didn't help my legs to go up.
I didn't want to do that, but I just kept going longer.
I'll be happy to receive your amazing record.
Yes, but our goal is 150 jumps, so we will do our best!
Infinite jump showdown
Nearly Equal Joy Mizuki Oshidashi
Mitsuki Oshida
Sweet Steady Mayumi Shiraishi
That being said, I will do my best to make this legwork banya.
Please give me your best regards.
Yes, I am that nervous, though,
I'll do my best, but if we don't miss our jumps, I'm sure we can go quite long!
I'll be higher than you!
Let's go! Infinite Jump Showdown, Group 5
Nearly Equal Joy Mizuki Oshida and Sweet Steady Mayumi Shiraishi
YYYY!
Let's start!
We did our best!
Two, three, four, five,
Take your time!
Yes, four, nine,
10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 2 3, 24, 25, 26, 27.
Good luck, Shiraishi!
Middle school track and field team
I'm a junior.
Yes, sir.
He did a great job.
Forty-eight, 49, 50, 51, 52.
We're at 52, so that means 51 times.
Mizuki Oeda, 51, Sweet Steady, Mayumi Shiraishi, 43.
Whole body! All of them!
How do you feel now?
I'm a little disappointed, but I had fun eating it.
I'm glad. I'm glad. Fun is the best.
I'm so frustrated! I'm so frustrated!
Did I drink too much water?
Well, that's all for now. Thank you very much.
And now we come to the sixth and final group.
Rina Yuki of Ukka is currently the provisional leader,
Her heart rate has been elevated since her last competition,
The doctor has decided that she needs to stay in a resting state.
Considering her physical condition, this endless jumping competition is dangerous for her.
This event has been ruled as dangerous.
What?
This event has been declared dangerous.
Until the very last minute.
I've been thinking about it with my trainer.
I've been thinking about it with my trainer so that I can focus all my energy on the fourth event.
I was told that if I left the third event, it would be the same again.
The finals started.
They lined up almost at the same time.
Organic effect
Organic.
The organic leader from Uganda wins.
What about organic?
Couldn't cover it with speed.
Organic leader eliminated
First standby cam.
Of course, some of us want to forget.
I've got fans coming all the way out here.
I know you're sad that I missed the third event.
I'm sure there must have been some sadness.
And even if you couldn't come yet...
I received many messages of support from those who couldn't make it.
I took their thoughts and feelings into consideration.
I hope to compete in the 4th event.
As of the end of the 6th group, 3rd overall, Nonoka Kazami, Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku
I'll do my best to make up for Rina-chan.
I'm going to do my best to reach 200 times.
I think it's tough to do it alone.
At first, you don't want to lose to your partner.
Now, let's see you, Ebisu Chugaku Kazamino!
Infinite jump showdown, group 6
Start the preparation!
Here we go!
Ten. Eleven. Twelve. Thirteen. Fourteen.
He said he didn't see the bar.
He said he doesn't look at the bar because he thinks it's too high.
He said he doesn't look at the bar because he thinks it's too high and it makes him fly too high.
23 24 25 26 27 28
Since this audition was scheduled, in addition to his usual training
I did 100 squats, drove 50 meters, and practiced even more!
Everyday without fail, training all year round.
running nearly 13 km if I continued.
50 Times.
I feel like this is the hardest time right now.
70 times.
We went over 70 times.
I was born in 2007 17
I'm okay, I'm okay.
81 Coming in over 80
Still jump stable.
Almost the same place
My torso is not wobbling
86 87 88 89
Constant rhythm 90
Come on, I see something a little different.
100 is coming up.
Ninety-four. Ninety-five. Ninety-six.
Ninety-seven.
Ninety-nine.
One hundred.
We've crossed the 100 mark.
There's a big round of applause for us.
But the target is still far away!
Next target is Yamamoto with 129!
110 times up.
We're up to 119, 120.
The rock dancer's record is 129.
123, 124, 125.
First, its provisional second place target
127, 128, 129, 132
131, 132, 133.
And then SK48
133 144 145
137 138 139
4 more to go
Catching up.
Victory is now assured.
How do you feel? How do you feel now?
Yes, I am. I was working hard, singing my favorite songs in my head, not thinking about jumping the whole time.
What were you playing?
I played a variety of songs, but the last song I played was a solo by Sakurayama, who has been supporting me.
I played it in my head as I worked hard.
Wow, I worked hard!
Emma!
That was fast!
Well, why are you standing so normal when you've jumped 150 times?
Nanakar!
The winner of the infinite jump showdown was Ebisu Chugaku Kazaminonaka!
She jumped more than 150 times!
I didn't expect such a win!
It was a great battle!
It's so much fun!
But you came in second!
I wanted first place.
I'm like, "What the hell?
You said you wouldn't cry until I cried.
Oh, my God.
Thank you very much.
Was it all going according to plan?
It was just as planned. It was totally painful, but I was okay.
I think I was able to make it this far with the help of Rina-chan and her power.
Thank you for watching!
New videos are being released one after another!
Please subscribe to our channel!